phpnuke.org 2019-04-19

# Phpnuke - privacy policy

We use cookies to give you the best experience. If you continue, we'll assume you accept to receive all cookies from our website.[privacy policy](https://downloads.phpnuke.org/documents/privacy_policy.html) __

## Summary

In this PHPNUKE GDPR Compliance Statement & Privacy Policy you can find out:

  1. About Us

  2. The Collection of Data (Including Personal Data) & GDPR

  3. What Types of Data Do We Collect & When?

  4. Is My Personal Data & Other Information Safe & Secure?

  5. How can I Access, Amend, Correct and/or Delete my Personal Data?

  6. International Data Transfers

  7. Disclosure of Personal Data

  8. How Long Do We Keep Your Information

  9. Our Cookies Policy

  10. Changes to this PHPNUKE GDPR Compliance Statement & Privacy Policy, & Cookies Policy

## About Us

Bibado Investments S.L , the company which operates PHPNUKE, provides Download Aggregation services to its customers.

Bibado Investments S.L has been launched in May 2012 and is a company incorporated in Spain with company number B83247627.  Our office is at Urano 9 Bajo A – 28925 (Alcorcon) Madrid, Spain.

## The Collection of Data (Including Personal Data) & GDPR

The EU General Data Protection Regulation EU 2016/679 (“GDPR”) comes into effect on 25thMay 2018 and will replace all the European Data Protection Laws. The GDPR strengthens and unifies data protection rights for individuals throughout the EU.

The GDPR is intended to give you more control over how companies such as PHPNUKE collect data from you and how it is used.  In particular GDPR focuses on data collected which is “Personal Data”; such personal data may be your email address, your first and last name, or your IP address.  Where we collect Personal Data this policy tells you where is it collected, the type of data that is collected, the legal basis upon which we process that data, the reason for collecting the data, and the use we make of the data.  Notes are also provided which provide more information on the processing of that particular data source.

## What Types of Data do we Collect & When?

Below sets out the data that PHPNUKE gathers from our website visitors and our users.  We detail below when we collect data, the type of data we collect and then what we do with that data and why.

### Signing-up for a PHPNUKE account

Point of Collection:

| 

Signing-up for a PHPNUKE account  
  
---|---  
  
Type of Personal Data Collected:

| 

Upon sign-up we collect:

  * email address;

  * password; and/or

  * IP address

Basis for Processing:

| 

The basis upon which we process your personal data is as follows:

  * when you sign-up for a PHPNUKE account you are giving us your clear consent that we may process your personal data for those specific purposes set-out in our Terms & Conditions and this Privacy Policy; and/or

  * the processing of your personal data is necessary for the contract you have entered into with us, and enables us to deliver PHPNUKE service to you.

Reason for Collection:

| 

The data collected enables us to create your account and give you a unique and secure way of logging into your account  
  
Use of Data Collected:

| 

We will use this data to:

  * enable you to login securely to your account

  * send you emails relating to your account and the PHPNUKE service including by way of example, on-boarding emails, product updates, and

Notes:

| 

  * This data is not shared with any third parties.

  * If you do not wish to receive these emails please contact us.

  * PHPNUKE account passwords are encrypted using Bcrypt; we do not store raw passwords.

  * This data is processed and stored within France.

### Your Navigation & Use of the PHPNUKE Website & Service 

Point of Collection:

| 

Your Navigation & Use of the PHPNUKE Website & Service   
  
---|---  
  
Type of Data Collected:

| 

When you arrive at the PHPNUKE website we may use visitor analytics tool to track how you arrived on our website, how you navigate through the website and on to sign-up.

We may also track the use you make of the PHPNUKE service, including by way of example, when and how you make use of individual features, when and how you set-up tests and/or alerts.

-a. The domain name of the Internet service provider (ISP) and/or the IP address that gives them access to the network.

–b. The date and time of access to our website.

-c. The internet address from which the link that that leads to our website originated.

–d. The type of browser client.

-e. The client’s operating system.

-f - ip address

Basis for Processing:

| 

The basis upon which we process your Navigational Data is as follows:

It is stored in the system logs for 7 days, for service and maintenance tasks.  
  
Reason for Collection:

| 

The Navigational Data collected enables us to understand how you and/or our users as a whole make use of the PHPNUKE website and service.  
  
Use of Data Collected:

| 

We may use the Navigational Data collected to:

  * understand how you and our other users arrive at the PHPNUKE website and navigate our website;

  * understand how you use the product;

  * use your data individually and/or aggregated to improve the usability of the product; and/or

  * use your data to answer your customer support queries.

Notes:

| 

  * When you sign-up for a PHPNUKE account the Navigational Data which has been collected via Google Analytics.  Up until the point of account creation (at which point processing consent is given), we do not tie any of your Navigational Data to your Personal Data.

  * We can opt-out of Google Analytics by clicking [here](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).  This will not stop you from experiencing the full benefits of the PHPNUKE website and service.

  * Save as set out above, we do not share your information with any third parties.

## Is My Personal Data & Other Information Safe & Secure?

We employ a number of steps-and-measures to ensure that all information and Personal Data we collect is protected from unauthorised access, use and/or disclosure.

As well as putting in place technological security measures, we also ensure that our entire team are trained in data security and that each of them have contractual obligations in their contracts of employment not to disclose information to anyone who is not entitled to have it.

## How can I Access, Amend, Correct and/or Delete my Personal Data?

You have the right at any time to access any Personal Data we hold about you, and where you feel the Personal Information that we hold is not correct, to request that the Personal Information is corrected.  You also have the right to have your Personal Information deleted.

All of the Personal Information, along with other data collected (as noted in the table above) is information that you can access, amend or delete by logging into your PHPNUKE Account.

If you have any questions about accessing, correcting, amending, or deleting your information then you can contact us.

## International Data Transfers

Any and all Personal Data that we collect from within the EU/ European Economic Area (EEA) and Switzerland is processed and stored within the UK.

In the event that Personal Data is transferred outside of the EU/EEA and/or Switzerland, we ensure that at all times that we provide the same level of privacy protection as is required by the EU-US Privacy Shield framework and/or any other framework determined by the European Commission to provide adequate protection for data transfers from the EU and/or Switzerland to the US.

## Third-Party Service Providers

We share information, including personal information, with our third-party service providers that we use to provide hosting for and maintenance of our Websites, customer service, application development, backup, storage, payment processing, analytics and other services for us. These third-party service providers may have access to or process your personal information for the purpose of providing these services for us. We do not permit our third-party service providers to use the personal information that we share with them for their marketing purposes or for any other purpose than in connection with the services they provide to us.

We may use [third-party advertising companies](http://d1jyv7fx66f9gf.cloudfront.net/pp.html) to serve ads when you visit our website

## Disclosure of Personal Data

We will not disclose your Personal Data to any third party unless as otherwise explicitly set out in this PHPNUKE GDPR Compliance Statement & Privacy Policy.  We may however at times be required by law, a competent regulatory authority, by a court, to disclose your Personal Information.   Where this occurs we will where it is practical for us to do so and/or to the extent that we are not otherwise restricted from doing so, notify you before disclosing your Personal Data.

## How Long Do We Keep Your Information

The length of time we keep your Personal Data and other information will depend on both the nature of the information we have gathered and the use we make of that information.

Unless we are required by law to keep your Personal Data and other information for a certain amount of time, we will not ordinarily keep your information longer than is necessary, given the purpose for what that information for collected by us.

## Our Cookies Policy

### What is a Cookie?

A cookie is a small text file, which is unique to you and allows the PHPNUKE Websites to recognise your computer or any such other device which you may use from time-to-time for browsing the Internet (collectively “Your Computer”).

We may use cookies and other “tags” (sometimes referred to as “web-beacons” or “pixel-tags”) (collectively “Cookie(s)”) to provide you with a more personalised service on the PHPNUKE Websites or to aid or track your navigation around our website.

If you do choose not to accept any of our Cookies some of the functionality or personalised version of the PHPNUKE Websites may not be available to you.

### When Do We Use Cookies?

When you register to receive information on the PHPNUKE Websites and/or register to use the PHPNUKE Services we may allocate a Cookie to Your Computer (“Registration Cookie”).

A Registration Cookie may hold any information collection during your registration or sign-up and allows us to recognise you and provide you with the information or services that you require. If your browser is not set to accept Cookies you may not be able to register for and/or sign-up for the PHPNUKE Services.

In addition to Registration Cookies we may from time-to-time use other types of Cookie to gather information. Such Cookies may include, but not be limited to “session-based” Cookies which are allotted to Your Computer for the duration of your visit to the PHPNUKE Websites, but will be deleted when you close down your Internet browser.

All use of Cookie gathered information is made in accordance with our PHPNUKE GDPR Compliance Statement & Privacy Policy.

## Changes to this PHPNUKE GDPR Compliance Statement & Privacy Policy, & Cookies Policy

This PHPNUKE GDPR Compliance Statement & Privacy Policy, along with our Cookies Policy, may be modified from time-to-time.  We recommend that you regularly review this page to ensure that you are aware of any changes made to it.

You will be bound by any changes to this PHPNUKE GDPR Compliance Statement & Privacy Policy from the moment you make any use of the PHPNUKE service after amendments have been made.

In the event that we make any material changes to this PHPNUKE GDPR Compliance Statement & Privacy Policy we will take reasonable efforts to notify you of those changes, by way of example only, whether through in-app notification or by email.

## PHPNUKE GDPR Compliance Statement & Privacy Policy – Last Updated 24 April 2018
